TREVER OVESON

Springville, UT 84663

Phone: 385-233-8011 | Email: toveson9522@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/trever-oveson / | github.com/toveson | https://toveson.github.io/react-portfolio/#/

SUMMARY

Full stack web developer with a decade of experience in telecommunications, inventory management, quality control, and team management. I communicate effectively, can lead a team, or contribute as a team member. I work hard and help others to meet deadlines.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML, CSS, Javascript

Skills: React.js, Material UI, Bulma, UIKit, Handlebars, Bootstrap, MongoDB, MySQL,

Passport, Node, JQuery, Express.js

PROJECTS

Update to taskably 2

Taskably-2.0 https://github.com/toveson/taskably-2.0 | https://arcane-wildwood-67330.herokuapp.com/

- A program to manage products, orders, employees, and customers
- Tools used: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bulma
- Developed this in collaboration with a group of developers

Weather-Dashboard github.com/toveson/Weather-Dashboard/toveson.github.io/Weather-Dashboard/

- This application allows the user to search a city and receive detailed, current weather information as well as a five-day forecast.
- Tools used: Bootstrap, Jquery, moment, HTML, Javascript

Day-Planner | toveson.github.io/Day-Planner | toveson.github.io/Day-Planner/

- This application gives users the ability to easily save appointments to hour time blocks.
- Tools used: Bootstrap, Font AwesomeTools, Jquery, Moment, HTML, Javascript, CSS

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Teaching Assistant, University of Utah, Salt Lake City, Utah

2021 - Current

• Assist instructor by helping students work through new material

Inventory Specialist, Clear Home, Orem, Utah

2011 - Current

- 2011 installation technician and was promoted to a lead technician position 2013
- 2017 I moved into a corporate role assessing quality control on installations.
- 2018 promoted to regional field supervisor
- 2019-current Inventory specialist

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Certification: The University of Utah, Salt Lake City, UT, January 2021